// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Who was First secretary general of United Nations?",
    answer: "Trigve Li",
    options: [
      "Trigve Li",
      "James Bond",
      "Donald Trump",
      "Narendra Modi"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Name of the first country to launch the satellite into space?",
    answer: "Russia",
    options: [
      "India",
      "Russia",
      "Japan",
      "America"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which country won first World Cup Football?",
    answer: "Uruguay in 1930",
    options: [
      "America in 1930",
      "Africa in 1930",
      "Uruguay in 1930",
      "Japan in 1930"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "First Woman Prime Minister Of Any Muslim Country?",
    answer: "Benazir Bhutto (Pakistan)",
    options: [
      "Indira Gandhi",
      "Sarojini Naidu",
      "John Mery",
      "Benazir Bhutto (Pakistan)"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Name of the first country to issue paper currency?",
    answer: "China",
    options: [
      "India",
      "China",
      "Russia",
      "Japan"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Name of the first Country to make a constitution?",
    answer: "USA",
    options: [
      "USA",
      "Brazil",
      "Russia",
      "Britain"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Who was the first person to sail around the world?",
    answer: "Ferdinand Magellan",
    options: [
      "Abrahim Lichon",
      "Ferdinand Magellan",
      "Vaskodigama",
      "Royal Bird"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "First men to fly an airplane?",
    answer: "Wright Brothers",
    options: [
      "Wright Brothers",
      "John Mery",
      "Rosy John",
      "W. H. Donald"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Name of the first man to go into space?",
    answer: "Major Yuri Gagarin (USSR)",
    options: [
      "Major Yuri Gagarin (USSR)",
      "Sandeep Snadhu",
      "Rajesh Sharma",
      "Mahendra Singh Dhoni"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Who won first Nobel prize for physics?",
    answer: "W.K. Roentgen (Germany)",
    options: [
      "David Dhawan",
      "Nelson Mandela",
      "Charu Stephan",
      "W.K. Roentgen (Germany)"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];